# ROEY REGEV | רועי רגב

Graphic design: UI/UX | motion | animation | storytelling | (coding)

**ABOUT ME** 

An odd creature in the design world. A versatile designer with marketing & product experience, business management education and some coding knowledge that likes to help building products in any way that's needed. Plus, I tend to stay in places I love for a long time. Strong opinions, low ego, open mind, patient demeanor.

+972-54-4560099 []

roeyregev@gmail.com ☑

Givatayim, Israel 🙃

https://personal-website-production-96b2.up.railway.app/

• •

# **SKILLS**

- Storytelling: Simplifying and conveying complex concepts for clients and users
- High professional versatility with the ability to contribute across multiple design disciplines (UI/UX, motion, animation)
- Strong understanding of the interplay between business objectives, dev constraints, and design principles
- Rapid learner. I figure out things. I vision the goal and learn what I need in order to create it.
- Integrating motion and animation into UI flows to enhance user experience and product storytelling
- Experience navigating the various stages of startup growth, from initial development to scaling

#### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

- UX/UI tools: Figma & Sketch
- Adobe CC (with focus on After Effects, Photoshop and Illustrator)
- Coding: Html, CSS, SCSS, React, NextJS, Angular, Javascript, Node-js, MySQL

## **EDUCATION**

2005-2009 - B. Design & Education - Wizo Design Academy

**2017-2019 - MA Business Management** (Technology, Innovation & Entrepreneurship) - TAU

**Feb 2023- Feb 2024 - Full Stack Development course** - John Bryce Academy

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# 2018-present - Stuff That Works

Stuffthatworks.health

- Designed and implemented new features and iterated on existing features for web and iOS platforms as the product evolved
- Collaborated closely with development teams throughout the design and implementation process
- Educational & promotional animations, UI motion design, social media campaigns, ads campaigns, board/business presentations
- Anything that was needed in a small startup to help push the product/company forward.

# 2010-2018 - Waze/Google

- Marketing design educational & promotional animations, motion design, social media campaigns, ads campaigns
- UI/UX (web, iOS, Android) and working with the dev team

#### 2009-2010 - Not From Here branding studio

notfromhere.net

· Junior designer - Logos, branding, web pages, printed assets

## **ACHIEVEMENTS**

## 2017 - Best marketing animation clip (Welcome to Waze Map Editor)

- Assif contest - Animix animation festival, Tel Aviv

• • •